{
    "id": "cb0939fc76cd44d38fd51ee5d164713e",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "One must learn to adapt oneself …………………. new circumstances.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must adhere ………………….. the truth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to finish the work within the time I have allotted ………………….. you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am grateful ………………… your help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sorry ………………… my inability to accept your invitation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The conversation reverted ………………… . the original topic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He succumbed ………………….. his injuries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The soldier yielded ………………… the enemy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This style of writing is characteristic …………………. Dickens.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must always be cautious ………………….. giving offence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}